//These questions were created in collaboration with classmate Dustin Knowles

var questionBank = [
  // Question 1
  {
    question: "What do you need to write to change font style in CSS?",
    selection: ["All the below", "font-family", "font-weight", "font color"],
    answer: "font-family",
  },

  // Question 2
  {
    question:
      "Where in an HTML document is the correct place to refer to an internal style sheet?",
    selection: [
      "in the <body> section",
      "in the <head> section",
      "at the end of the document",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "in the <head> section",
  },

  // Question 3
  {
    question:
      "What is the correct HTML for referring to an external CSS stylesheet?",
    selection: [
      "<link rel='stylesheet' type='text/css' href='mystyle.css'>",
      "<stylesheet>mystyle.css</stylesheet>",
      "<stylesheet>mystyle</stylesheet>",
    ],
    answer: "<link rel='stylesheet' type='text/css' href='mystyle.css'>",
  },

  // Question 4
  {
    question: "What does a <div> tag do?",
    selection: [
      "The <div> tag defines a division or a section in an HTML document.",
      "The <div> tag is used to group block-elements to format them with CSS.",
      "The <div> tag divides the nation into absolute peril.",
      "A and B",
    ],
    answer: "A and B",
  },

  // Question 5
  {
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    selection: [
      "Hot Tamales Make Love",
      "Hypertext Markup Language",
      "Hyper Tense Marker Literals",
      "Hypertext Mobile Language",
    ],
    answer: "Hypertext Markup Language",
  },

  // Question 6
  {
    question: "What is the correct format for a 'comment' in HTML?",
    selection: [
      "/*  comment  */",
      "<$-- comment -->",
      "<!-- comment -->",
      " #comment",
    ],
    answer: "<!-- comment -->",
  },

  // Question 7
  {
    question:
      "What index number is Kansas City Chiefs? var nflTeams = ['Los Angeles Rams', 'Chicago Bears', 'Philadelphia Eagles', 'Kansas City Chiefs']",
    selection: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
    answer: "3",
  },

  // Question 8
  {
    question: "What function gets you a random math number?",
    selection: [
      "Math.floor();",
      "Math.round();",
      "Math.split();",
      "Math.random();",
    ],
    answer: "Math.random();",
  },

  // Question 9
  {
    question:
      "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
    selection: ["commas", "curly brackets", "quotes", "parentheses"],
    answer: "quotes",
  },

  // Question 10
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following are examples of JavaScript variable data types?",
    selection: ["number", "null", "Boolean", "All of the above"],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
];
